Subscribe to the YouTube channel
AllBankQuarters.com and press the bell icon
to watch the video first.
Friends, in this video we will tell you
important information related to your IDFC Bank account. Friends, today we will
tell you how you can use
Corporate Internet Banking in your ICICI Bank current account.
For this, you must have a
login ID and password. If
you don't have a login ID and password,
you can click on "Generate." So
let's start the video and
show you how you can generate your login ID and
password. For this, you need to
type "IDBI Bank" and "
President Banking" into Google or whatever you use. As soon as you type,
you will see an
interface open where
you will need to search for "Corporate ID" and "
User Defined" to log in. After that, you
can log in to your Corporate Internet Banking from here by clicking on "Apna Papad" and "Profit" button. If you do
n't have a login ID, there is
an option below where it
says "No Your Login ID." You can click on this button to create
your login ID.  You
can send a message and for this you will
enter your account number here, then you
will enter your mobile number and
click on the submit button, then you will
receive an SMS on your mobile in which
your login ID is given, so you will
note down your login ID from here and
after that the next process is to generate your password, to
generate the password you will
see that here you are shown the option of forget password,
so you can generate
your password by clicking on the option of forget password,
as you will
generate the password, here it is asking for your login
ID, so you will click next here
and after that you will generate your new password here, so
friends, in this way you have
generated your passport, now if you
want to generate the PIN of your ATM card, then you will see on the home page you will
see the option of debit card PIN, by
clicking on it you will verify your debit card number
and after that the digit number of the debit card
and by
clicking on the submit button you can generate your PIN here, so
friends, this is a simple
process of using your corporate internet banking,
if you liked this video
So like this video and
subscribe to our channel friends
if you are still
facing any problem in logging into Corporate Internet Banking
or if you
want any other information related to your account then you
can tell us by commenting, we will
definitely give you information on this topic and friends if
you have not subscribed to this channel yet then do
subscribe to this channel and
also press the first icon so that
you keep getting notifications of our upcoming videos so that that's all for today
thank you friends
[Music]